{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . #\n. # . . . .\n. . . # . .\n. . . . . .\n. G . . . #\n. # A . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left","env":"# . . . . #\n. # . . . .\n. . . # . .\n. . . . . .\n. G . . . #\n. # A . . .\n","size":6,"actions":"up left","numeric_actions":[0,3],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[5,2],"goal_pos":[4,1],"obstacles":[[5,1],[4,5],[0,5],[2,3],[1,1],[0,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . .\n. . . . .\n. # # A #\n. # . G .\n. . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down","env":". . . . .\n. . . . .\n. # # A #\n. # . G .\n. . # . .\n","size":5,"actions":"down","numeric_actions":[2],"n_steps":1,"start_pos":[2,3],"goal_pos":[3,3],"obstacles":[[2,4],[2,2],[2,1],[4,2],[3,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . . . . .\n# . . . # . . # .\n. . # . . . # # #\n. . . . . # . . .\n. . # . . . . . .\n# . . . A . . . .\n# . . # . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . G . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right right down down","env":"# . . . . . . . .\n# . . . # . . # .\n. . # . . . # # #\n. . . . . # . . .\n. . # . . . . . .\n# . . . A . . . .\n# . . # . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . G . .\n","size":9,"actions":"down right right down down","numeric_actions":[2,1,1,2,2],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[5,4],"goal_pos":[8,6],"obstacles":[[1,7],[1,0],[3,5],[6,0],[6,3],[2,6],[2,2],[2,7],[4,2],[0,0],[6,7],[2,8],[5,0],[2,2],[1,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . . #\n. . # . # . .\n. . . A . . .\n. . . . # . .\n. . . . . # .\n. G . # . . .\n. . . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left down left down down","env":"# . . . . . #\n. . # . # . .\n. . . A . . .\n. . . . # . .\n. . . . . # .\n. G . # . . .\n. . . . . . #\n","size":7,"actions":"left down left down down","numeric_actions":[3,2,3,2,2],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[2,3],"goal_pos":[5,1],"obstacles":[[0,0],[3,4],[1,4],[5,3],[6,6],[1,2],[0,6],[4,5]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . . . # # # . .\n# . . . . . . # #\n# . . # . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . #\n. . # . . . . . .\n. . G . A . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left","env":". # # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . . . # # # . .\n# . . . . . . # #\n# . . # . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . #\n. . # . . . . . .\n. . G . A . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"left left","numeric_actions":[3,3],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[7,4],"goal_pos":[7,2],"obstacles":[[4,8],[0,1],[3,7],[2,4],[4,0],[4,3],[3,0],[6,2],[5,3],[5,8],[2,5],[5,3],[0,2],[3,8],[2,6],[1,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . A .\n. . # . . .\n. . . . . .\n. # . # . .\n. . . G . #\n. # . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down down down left","env":". . . . A .\n. . # . . .\n. . . . . .\n. # . # . .\n. . . G . #\n. # . . . .\n","size":6,"actions":"down down down down left","numeric_actions":[2,2,2,2,3],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[0,4],"goal_pos":[4,3],"obstacles":[[4,5],[4,5],[1,2],[5,1],[3,3],[3,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . # . . . .\n. . # . # . . .\n. # . # . # # .\n. . . # A . . .\n. . . . . . G .\n. # . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right right","env":"# . . # . . . .\n. . # . # . . .\n. # . # . # # .\n. . . # A . . .\n. . . . . . G .\n. # . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n","size":8,"actions":"down right right","numeric_actions":[2,1,1],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[3,4],"goal_pos":[4,6],"obstacles":[[5,7],[2,5],[3,3],[2,3],[2,6],[0,0],[1,2],[2,1],[1,4],[2,1],[5,1],[0,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # . . . . .\n. # . # . . . . #\n# . # . . . . A .\n. . . . # . # . #\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . . . # G . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . # # . . . . .\n. . . . # # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left down down down","env":". . . # . . . . .\n. # . # . . . . #\n# . # . . . . A .\n. . . . # . # . #\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . . . # G . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . # # . . . . .\n. . . . # # . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"left left down down down","numeric_actions":[3,3,2,2,2],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[2,7],"goal_pos":[5,5],"obstacles":[[7,3],[8,5],[3,6],[3,8],[3,4],[1,8],[6,6],[0,3],[7,2],[8,4],[5,4],[4,8],[1,3],[2,0],[1,1],[2,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # . . . . #\n. . . A . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . #\nG . . . . . # . .\n. . . # . . . . .\n# . . . # . # . .\n. # . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . # .\n. . . # . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left down down left left","env":". . . # . . . . #\n. . . A . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . #\nG . . . . . # . .\n. . . # . . . . .\n# . . . # . # . .\n. # . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . # .\n. . . # . . . . #\n","size":9,"actions":"left down down left left","numeric_actions":[3,2,2,3,3],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[1,3],"goal_pos":[3,0],"obstacles":[[1,5],[6,1],[0,8],[5,0],[8,8],[1,8],[5,4],[0,8],[8,3],[4,3],[3,6],[2,8],[0,3],[6,8],[5,6],[7,7]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. A . # . . # .\n. # . # . . . .\n. # . . . . # .\n. # . G . . . .\n# . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # . .\n# . # . . . . #\n. . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down down down right","env":". A . # . . # .\n. # . # . . . .\n. # . . . . # .\n. # . G . . . .\n# . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # . .\n# . # . . . . #\n. . . . . . . .\n","size":8,"actions":"right down down down right","numeric_actions":[1,2,2,2,1],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[0,1],"goal_pos":[3,3],"obstacles":[[2,1],[3,1],[4,0],[2,6],[0,6],[6,7],[0,3],[6,2],[1,1],[1,3],[6,0],[5,5]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # # . .\n. . # . . . .\n. # # . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n# . # . . . .\n. G . # . . .\n. . . . . # A\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left left down left left up left","env":". . . # # . .\n. . # . . . .\n. # # . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n# . # . . . .\n. G . # . . .\n. . . . . # A\n","size":7,"actions":"up left left down left left up left","numeric_actions":[0,3,3,2,3,3,0,3],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[6,6],"goal_pos":[5,1],"obstacles":[[6,5],[1,2],[4,0],[0,3],[2,2],[0,4],[2,1],[4,2],[5,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . # . # #\n. . . . . . .\n. # . . # . .\n. . . . # . .\n. A G . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right","env":". . # . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . # . # #\n. . . . . . .\n. # . . # . .\n. . . . # . .\n. A G . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"right","numeric_actions":[1],"n_steps":1,"start_pos":[6,1],"goal_pos":[6,2],"obstacles":[[2,6],[2,3],[0,2],[4,4],[0,6],[4,1],[2,5],[5,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . A . . . .\n. . . # . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . . .\n. . G . # . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n# . . . . . # . # .\n# . . . # # . . . .\n# . . # . # . . . #\n. # . . # . # . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left left down down down","env":". . . . . A . . . .\n. . . # . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . . .\n. . G . # . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n# . . . . . # . # .\n# . . . # # . . . .\n# . . # . # . . . #\n. # . . # . # . . #\n","size":10,"actions":"left left left down down down","numeric_actions":[3,3,3,2,2,2],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[0,5],"goal_pos":[3,2],"obstacles":[[8,5],[8,9],[4,0],[1,3],[6,0],[7,5],[3,4],[7,4],[5,9],[9,1],[9,9],[9,4],[2,0],[6,6],[6,8],[8,0],[9,6],[8,3],[7,0],[4,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . .\n. . . . .\n# . . . .\nG . A . .\n. # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left","env":". # . . .\n. . . . .\n# . . . .\nG . A . .\n. # . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"left left","numeric_actions":[3,3],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[3,2],"goal_pos":[3,0],"obstacles":[[2,0],[0,1],[4,1],[4,1],[4,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . . # . .\n. . . # # # . .\n. # # . G . . .\n. # A . . . . .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . # .\n. # . . . . . .\n. . . . # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right up","env":". # . . . # . .\n. . . # # # . .\n. # # . G . . .\n. # A . . . . .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . # .\n. # . . . . . .\n. . . . # . . .\n","size":8,"actions":"right right up","numeric_actions":[1,1,0],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[3,2],"goal_pos":[2,4],"obstacles":[[2,2],[5,6],[0,5],[6,1],[2,1],[7,4],[1,3],[3,1],[1,5],[0,1],[4,3],[1,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . . #\n# # G . # . . .\n. A . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . #\n# . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . #\n. # . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up","env":". . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . . #\n# # G . # . . .\n. A . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . #\n# . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . #\n. # . . . . . .\n","size":8,"actions":"right up","numeric_actions":[1,0],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[3,1],"goal_pos":[2,2],"obstacles":[[2,4],[4,7],[2,0],[2,4],[2,1],[4,0],[5,5],[1,2],[6,7],[7,1],[5,0],[1,7]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # . . # .\n. . . . . . . #\n. # . . . A . .\n. . G # # . . .\n. # . . . . . .\n. . . # # . . .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left left down","env":". . . # . . # .\n. . . . . . . #\n. # . . . A . .\n. . G # # . . .\n. # . . . . . .\n. . . # # . . .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n","size":8,"actions":"left left left down","numeric_actions":[3,3,3,2],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[2,5],"goal_pos":[3,2],"obstacles":[[4,1],[5,3],[2,1],[7,7],[0,3],[1,7],[5,4],[3,3],[0,6],[6,3],[3,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . # . . # . . #\n. . . # . . . # . .\n. . # G . . . . . .\n. . # . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n# . . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . A # . .\n. . # . # . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left left up left up up up","env":". . . . . . . . # .\n. . . # . . # . . #\n. . . # . . . # . .\n. . # G . . . . . .\n. . # . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n# . . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . A # . .\n. . # . # . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"up left left up left up up up","numeric_actions":[0,3,3,0,3,0,0,0],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[8,6],"goal_pos":[3,3],"obstacles":[[6,9],[4,4],[6,9],[2,7],[7,3],[1,6],[1,9],[9,4],[3,2],[0,8],[7,3],[4,2],[6,0],[1,3],[6,9],[2,3],[8,7],[4,2],[9,2],[5,7]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . G\n. . . # .\n. # . # A\n# . . # .\n. . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up up","env":". . . . G\n. . . # .\n. # . # A\n# . . # .\n. . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"up up","numeric_actions":[0,0],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[2,4],"goal_pos":[0,4],"obstacles":[[2,1],[3,0],[1,3],[3,3],[2,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . #\n# . . . . # . . .\n# # . . . G # . .\n. . # # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n# . . A . . . . .\n. . . # . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right up up up","env":". . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . #\n# . . . . # . . .\n# # . . . G # . .\n. . # # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n# . . A . . . . .\n. . . # . . # . .\n","size":9,"actions":"right right up up up","numeric_actions":[1,1,0,0,0],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[7,3],"goal_pos":[4,5],"obstacles":[[1,0],[8,6],[2,8],[1,8],[2,3],[8,3],[4,1],[4,0],[5,3],[5,2],[4,6],[3,5],[3,0],[7,0],[1,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. A . # . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . # .\n. G . . . . . . . #\n. # . . # . # . . #\n. # . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. # . . . # . . . .\n. . . # # . . . . .\n. . # . . . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down down left","env":". A . # . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . # .\n. G . . . . . . . #\n. # . . # . # . . #\n. # . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. # . . . # . . . .\n. . . # # . . . . .\n. . # . . . . # . .\n","size":10,"actions":"right down down left","numeric_actions":[1,2,2,3],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[0,1],"goal_pos":[2,1],"obstacles":[[2,9],[9,7],[3,6],[3,4],[5,9],[1,1],[3,9],[9,2],[4,1],[8,3],[8,4],[5,9],[0,3],[7,1],[4,7],[7,5],[3,1],[3,9],[1,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. G . . .\n. . . . .\n. . # . #\n# . # . .\n# . . A .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left up up up up","env":". G . . .\n. . . . .\n. . # . #\n# . # . .\n# . . A .\n","size":5,"actions":"left left up up up up","numeric_actions":[3,3,0,0,0,0],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[4,3],"goal_pos":[0,1],"obstacles":[[3,2],[2,4],[4,0],[2,2],[3,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . .\n. # . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . # #\n. . . # . . .\n. . . . G . #\n. . # . # A .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left","env":". . # . . . .\n. # . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . # #\n. . . # . . .\n. . . . G . #\n. . # . # A .\n","size":7,"actions":"up left","numeric_actions":[0,3],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[6,5],"goal_pos":[5,4],"obstacles":[[1,1],[6,4],[5,6],[4,3],[3,5],[6,2],[3,6],[0,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . A # G . # .\n. . # . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . # . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . . .\n. . . # # # . . # .\n. . . . # . . . . #\n. . # . . . . . # #\n. # . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right right up","env":". # . . A # G . # .\n. . # . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . # . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . . .\n. . . # # # . . # .\n. . . . # . . . . #\n. . # . . . . . # #\n. # . . . . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"down right right up","numeric_actions":[2,1,1,0],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[0,4],"goal_pos":[0,6],"obstacles":[[4,0],[8,8],[6,5],[6,8],[7,9],[7,4],[4,3],[1,9],[9,1],[1,2],[0,5],[8,2],[7,4],[0,1],[7,9],[0,8],[6,4],[5,1],[6,3],[8,9]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . .\n# . . . . # .\n. # . . . . .\n. . . A . # .\n. . # . . . .\n. . . . . . #\nG . . . . # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down left down left left","env":". . # . . . .\n# . . . . # .\n. # . . . . .\n. . . A . # .\n. . # . . . .\n. . . . . . #\nG . . . . # .\n","size":7,"actions":"down down left down left left","numeric_actions":[2,2,3,2,3,3],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[3,3],"goal_pos":[6,0],"obstacles":[[1,0],[1,5],[3,5],[2,1],[0,2],[0,2],[4,2],[6,5],[5,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . A . .\n. . . . G .\n. . . . # .\n. . . . # .\n. # . . # .\n. . # # # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right","env":". . . A . .\n. . . . G .\n. . . . # .\n. . . . # .\n. # . . # .\n. . # # # .\n","size":6,"actions":"down right","numeric_actions":[2,1],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[0,3],"goal_pos":[1,4],"obstacles":[[5,2],[4,4],[4,1],[5,3],[3,4],[5,4],[2,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . . # .\n. . . . . # # #\n. . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . # . . # . #\n# . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . # .\n. . A . . G . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right","env":"# . . . . . # .\n. . . . . # # #\n. . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . # . . # . #\n# . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . # .\n. . A . . G . .\n","size":8,"actions":"right right right","numeric_actions":[1,1,1],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[7,2],"goal_pos":[7,5],"obstacles":[[5,0],[0,6],[4,5],[1,6],[6,6],[4,7],[2,5],[1,5],[4,2],[0,0],[1,7],[6,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . A . . .\n# . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . #\n# . . . . . .\n. . . # . # .\n. . G . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left down down down down down down","env":". . . A . . .\n# . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . #\n# . . . . . .\n. . . # . # .\n. . G . . . #\n","size":7,"actions":"left down down down down down down","numeric_actions":[3,2,2,2,2,2,2],"n_steps":7,"start_pos":[0,3],"goal_pos":[6,2],"obstacles":[[1,0],[5,5],[5,3],[3,6],[4,0],[6,6],[6,6],[3,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . .\n. . . . #\n. . G . #\n. # . A .\n# . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left up","env":". . . . .\n. . . . #\n. . G . #\n. # . A .\n# . . . #\n","size":5,"actions":"left up","numeric_actions":[3,0],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[3,3],"goal_pos":[2,2],"obstacles":[[1,4],[2,4],[4,4],[4,0],[3,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . A .\n. . . . . . .\n# . . . . # .\n# . . . # . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. # . . # G .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left down down left down down right right down down","env":". . . . . A .\n. . . . . . .\n# . . . . # .\n# . . . # . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. # . . # G .\n","size":7,"actions":"left down down left down down right right down down","numeric_actions":[3,2,2,3,2,2,1,1,2,2],"n_steps":10,"start_pos":[0,5],"goal_pos":[6,5],"obstacles":[[3,6],[6,1],[6,4],[3,0],[2,5],[2,0],[0,5],[3,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . # . # .\n# . . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . G A # . . . #\n. # # . . # # . .\n. # . # . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left","env":". . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . # . # .\n# . . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . G A # . . . #\n. # # . . # # . .\n. # . # . . . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"left","numeric_actions":[3],"n_steps":1,"start_pos":[6,3],"goal_pos":[6,2],"obstacles":[[1,5],[2,0],[0,3],[7,6],[5,1],[7,5],[3,6],[8,1],[6,4],[1,7],[2,5],[6,8],[3,6],[7,1],[8,3],[7,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . # .\n. . . . #\n. . # . .\n. . A . #\n. G . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down left","env":"# . . # .\n. . . . #\n. . # . .\n. . A . #\n. G . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"down left","numeric_actions":[2,3],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[3,2],"goal_pos":[4,1],"obstacles":[[3,4],[2,2],[0,3],[0,0],[1,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# # . . . . G\n# . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . #\n. # . A # . .\n. # . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up up up right up right up right","env":"# # . . . . G\n# . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . #\n. # . A # . .\n. # . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"up up up right up right up right","numeric_actions":[0,0,0,1,0,1,0,1],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[5,3],"goal_pos":[0,6],"obstacles":[[5,4],[4,6],[5,1],[0,0],[0,1],[1,0],[6,1],[5,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . # . . . #\n. . . # # . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n# . G . A . . .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . # .\n# . . . . # # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left","env":". # . # . . . #\n. . . # # . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n# . G . A . . .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . # .\n# . . . . # # .\n","size":8,"actions":"left left","numeric_actions":[3,3],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[4,4],"goal_pos":[4,2],"obstacles":[[0,7],[4,0],[7,0],[1,3],[5,3],[6,6],[3,7],[0,1],[7,5],[1,4],[0,3],[7,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # # . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . A . . . .\n. # . # . . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . . .\n# . . . . . # . # .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . # . . . . . .\n. G . . . # . # # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down down down left down left left down left down","env":". . # # . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . A . . . .\n. # . # . . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . . .\n# . . . . . # . # .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . # . . . . . .\n. G . . . # . # # .\n","size":10,"actions":"down down down down left down left left down left down","numeric_actions":[2,2,2,2,3,2,3,3,2,3,2],"n_steps":11,"start_pos":[2,5],"goal_pos":[9,1],"obstacles":[[3,1],[9,8],[9,5],[1,9],[0,3],[3,3],[6,8],[1,1],[2,3],[1,1],[5,3],[0,2],[3,6],[9,7],[8,3],[6,6],[6,0],[1,1],[3,9],[7,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . . #\nA . . # . . G\n. . . # . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . # . . .\n. . # . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right up right right down right right","env":"# . . . . . #\nA . . # . . G\n. . . # . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . # . . .\n. . # . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"right right up right right down right right","numeric_actions":[1,1,0,1,1,2,1,1],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[1,0],"goal_pos":[1,6],"obstacles":[[1,3],[1,3],[0,6],[5,2],[0,0],[2,3],[4,3],[0,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . A . . . . . #\n. . . . # . # . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # G .\n# . . # # . . . .\n. . . . # # . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . . # # . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right down down right right down","env":". . A . . . . . #\n. . . . # . # . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # G .\n# . . # # . . . .\n. . . . # # . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . . # # . . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"right right right down down right right down","numeric_actions":[1,1,1,2,2,1,1,2],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[0,2],"goal_pos":[3,7],"obstacles":[[4,4],[4,0],[1,4],[8,3],[7,8],[8,4],[3,6],[5,5],[5,4],[1,6],[0,8],[6,4],[2,1],[4,4],[4,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . # . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. # # . . . . G # #\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . # . . . #\n. # # . # . . . # .\n. . . . # . . . . .\n. . . A . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right up right up up up up up right","env":". . . . . . . . # .\n. . # . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. # # . . . . G # #\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . # . . . #\n. # # . # . . . # .\n. . . . # . . . . .\n. . . A . . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"right right up right up up up up up right","numeric_actions":[1,1,0,1,0,0,0,0,0,1],"n_steps":10,"start_pos":[9,3],"goal_pos":[3,7],"obstacles":[[6,9],[4,8],[8,4],[1,6],[7,2],[6,5],[0,8],[8,4],[7,1],[3,2],[4,8],[3,1],[5,7],[3,8],[1,2],[4,8],[7,8],[3,9],[7,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . . .\n. . . . . .\n# A . . . G\n. # . . . .\n# . . . # .\n. # . . # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right right","env":". # . . . .\n. . . . . .\n# A . . . G\n. # . . . .\n# . . . # .\n. # . . # .\n","size":6,"actions":"right right right right","numeric_actions":[1,1,1,1],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[2,1],"goal_pos":[2,5],"obstacles":[[4,0],[5,1],[4,4],[5,4],[0,1],[3,1],[2,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nA . . # . . . # . .\n. . . . . . # . # .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n# # . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # . # .\n. . # . . # . . . .\n. . # . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . G # . # .\n. . # # . . # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right down down right right down down down down right down down","env":"A . . # . . . # . .\n. . . . . . # . # .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n# # . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # . # .\n. . # . . # . . . .\n. . # . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . G # . # .\n. . # # . . # . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"right right down down right right down down down down right down down","numeric_actions":[1,1,2,2,1,1,2,2,2,2,1,2,2],"n_steps":13,"start_pos":[0,0],"goal_pos":[8,5],"obstacles":[[9,6],[6,8],[1,6],[5,5],[4,6],[4,6],[0,3],[4,8],[9,6],[0,7],[2,9],[8,8],[3,1],[5,2],[1,8],[9,3],[8,6],[9,2],[6,2],[3,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. # # # . # . . . .\n# # # # # . # . . .\n. . . # G . . . . .\n# . . . . . . # # .\n. . A . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up right up","env":". . . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. # # # . # . . . .\n# # # # # . # . . .\n. . . # G . . . . .\n# . . . . . . # # .\n. . A . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"right up right up","numeric_actions":[1,0,1,0],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[8,2],"goal_pos":[6,4],"obstacles":[[5,6],[7,0],[7,7],[5,3],[1,0],[4,1],[6,3],[4,1],[7,8],[5,2],[4,3],[4,5],[5,4],[5,4],[5,0],[1,9],[5,1],[4,2],[5,2],[3,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . #\nG . . . .\n. . A # #\n. . . . .\n# . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left left","env":". . . . #\nG . . . .\n. . A # #\n. . . . .\n# . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"up left left","numeric_actions":[0,3,3],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[2,2],"goal_pos":[1,0],"obstacles":[[2,4],[4,0],[4,0],[2,3],[0,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n# G . . . . .\n. A . . # . .\n. . . # . # .\n. # . . . # .\n. # . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up","env":"# . . . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n# G . . . . .\n. A . . # . .\n. . . # . # .\n. # . . . # .\n. # . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"up","numeric_actions":[0],"n_steps":1,"start_pos":[3,1],"goal_pos":[2,1],"obstacles":[[0,6],[6,1],[3,4],[4,3],[0,0],[5,1],[5,5],[4,5],[2,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . .\n. . # . . . #\n. . . # # . .\n. . # . # . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . G A\n# . # . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left","env":". . . . . . .\n. . # . . . #\n. . . # # . .\n. . # . # . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . G A\n# . # . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"left","numeric_actions":[3],"n_steps":1,"start_pos":[5,6],"goal_pos":[5,5],"obstacles":[[3,2],[2,4],[6,2],[3,4],[3,2],[6,0],[1,2],[1,6],[2,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. A . . . . # #\n. . . . . # # .\n. . G . # . . #\n. . # # . . . #\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down right","env":". A . . . . # #\n. . . . . # # .\n. . G . # . . #\n. . # # . . . #\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n","size":8,"actions":"down down right","numeric_actions":[2,2,1],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[0,1],"goal_pos":[2,2],"obstacles":[[3,2],[3,7],[7,7],[0,6],[2,4],[1,5],[2,7],[3,3],[5,6],[0,7],[1,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . .\n. . # # .\n# . G . .\n. . . . .\n# # . A .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left up","env":". . . . .\n. . # # .\n# . G . .\n. . . . .\n# # . A .\n","size":5,"actions":"up left up","numeric_actions":[0,3,0],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[4,3],"goal_pos":[2,2],"obstacles":[[4,0],[2,0],[4,1],[1,3],[1,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # .\n. A . . #\n# . . . G\n. . . . #\n. # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right right right","env":". . . # .\n. A . . #\n# . . . G\n. . . . #\n. # . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"down right right right","numeric_actions":[2,1,1,1],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[1,1],"goal_pos":[2,4],"obstacles":[[2,0],[3,4],[1,4],[4,1],[0,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # # . . . . . .\n# # . # . # . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\nA . . . . # # . .\n. . . . . # . . .\n. . . . # . . # .\n. . G . # . . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right down down down","env":". # # . . . . . .\n# # . # . # . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\nA . . . . # # . .\n. . . . . # . . .\n. . . . # . . # .\n. . G . # . . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n","size":9,"actions":"right right down down down","numeric_actions":[1,1,2,2,2],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[3,0],"goal_pos":[6,2],"obstacles":[[1,5],[6,4],[0,1],[7,6],[1,1],[0,2],[1,3],[5,7],[3,5],[5,4],[2,6],[5,7],[4,5],[3,6],[1,0],[8,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # # . .\nA . . . . . .\n. . . . G . #\n. . # . . # .\n. . . . . # .\n. # . . . . #\n. # . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down right right right","env":". . . # # . .\nA . . . . . .\n. . . . G . #\n. . # . . # .\n. . . . . # .\n. # . . . . #\n. # . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"right down right right right","numeric_actions":[1,2,1,1,1],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[1,0],"goal_pos":[2,4],"obstacles":[[4,5],[6,1],[0,3],[5,6],[3,5],[0,4],[2,6],[3,2],[5,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . .\n# . . . # . . #\n# . . . # . . .\n. # G # A . . .\n. . . . # . . .\n. . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up up up left left down down left down","env":". . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . .\n# . . . # . . #\n# . . . # . . .\n. # G # A . . .\n. . . . # . . .\n. . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . #\n","size":8,"actions":"right up up up left left down down left down","numeric_actions":[1,0,0,0,3,3,2,2,3,2],"n_steps":10,"start_pos":[4,4],"goal_pos":[4,2],"obstacles":[[2,0],[3,4],[3,0],[2,4],[4,1],[7,7],[4,3],[7,7],[0,6],[2,7],[6,4],[5,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . # . # . #\n. . # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . # . . . .\nG . . . . . # . . #\n. . # . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . A . # . . # .\n. . . . # . . . . .\n. . # # # . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left up up up left","env":"# . . . . # . # . #\n. . # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . # . . . .\nG . . . . . # . . #\n. . # . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . A . # . . # .\n. . . . # . . . . .\n. . # # # . . . . #\n","size":10,"actions":"left left up up up left","numeric_actions":[3,3,0,0,0,3],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[7,3],"goal_pos":[4,0],"obstacles":[[3,5],[7,5],[9,4],[0,5],[9,2],[9,9],[4,9],[0,7],[0,0],[7,8],[0,9],[5,7],[3,3],[1,2],[6,8],[8,4],[9,3],[5,2],[4,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nG . # . .\n. . . . .\n. . A . #\n. . # . .\n# . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left left up","env":"G . # . .\n. . . . .\n. . A . #\n. . # . .\n# . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"up left left up","numeric_actions":[0,3,3,0],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[2,2],"goal_pos":[0,0],"obstacles":[[4,0],[0,2],[2,4],[3,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . # .\n. # # . . .\n. . . . . .\n. . . . . #\n# A . . # .\n. . . . G .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right down right","env":". . . . # .\n. # # . . .\n. . . . . .\n. . . . . #\n# A . . # .\n. . . . G .\n","size":6,"actions":"right right down right","numeric_actions":[1,1,2,1],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[4,1],"goal_pos":[5,4],"obstacles":[[3,5],[4,0],[4,4],[0,4],[1,1],[1,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . #\nG . . . .\n. . . . .\n. A . . #\n# . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left up up","env":". . # . #\nG . . . .\n. . . . .\n. A . . #\n# . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"left up up","numeric_actions":[3,0,0],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[3,1],"goal_pos":[1,0],"obstacles":[[4,0],[0,4],[3,4],[0,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n# . . # . . .\n. G . # . A .\n. # . . . . #\n. . . # # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down left left left up left","env":". . # . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n# . . # . . .\n. G . # . A .\n. # . . . . #\n. . . # # . .\n","size":7,"actions":"down left left left up left","numeric_actions":[2,3,3,3,0,3],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[4,5],"goal_pos":[4,1],"obstacles":[[3,3],[3,0],[6,3],[5,1],[6,4],[4,3],[0,2],[6,3],[5,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . # .\n. . . . . # . .\n. # . . . A . .\n. . # . . . . #\n. . . . # . . .\n# . . # # . . .\n# . . . . . . .\n. . . . . G # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down down down down","env":". . # . . . # .\n. . . . . # . .\n. # . . . A . .\n. . # . . . . #\n. . . . # . . .\n# . . # # . . .\n# . . . . . . .\n. . . . . G # .\n","size":8,"actions":"down down down down down","numeric_actions":[2,2,2,2,2],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[2,5],"goal_pos":[7,5],"obstacles":[[5,0],[2,1],[1,5],[5,4],[3,7],[0,2],[6,0],[0,6],[3,2],[7,6],[5,3],[4,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . # . . . .\n# . . . . . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # # . . .\n# . # . . . . . . .\n. # # . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # . . .\n. . A . # . G . . .\n# . . . . . . # . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"up right right right down right","env":". . . . . # . . . .\n# . . . . . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # # . . .\n# . # . . . . . . .\n. # # . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . # . . .\n. . A . # . G . . .\n# . . . . . . # . #\n","size":10,"actions":"up right right right down right","numeric_actions":[0,1,1,1,2,1],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[8,2],"goal_pos":[8,6],"obstacles":[[4,2],[5,1],[9,7],[0,5],[1,0],[7,6],[8,4],[0,5],[3,6],[3,5],[1,9],[1,6],[5,8],[4,0],[9,0],[5,2],[3,6],[9,9],[5,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nA . . # . # .\n# . . # . . .\n. . . . . # G\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n# . . . . . .\n. # . # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down down right right right up right right down","env":"A . . # . # .\n# . . # . . .\n. . . . . # G\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n# . . . . . .\n. # . # . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"right down down right right right up right right down","numeric_actions":[1,2,2,1,1,1,0,1,1,2],"n_steps":10,"start_pos":[0,0],"goal_pos":[2,6],"obstacles":[[2,5],[1,3],[0,5],[6,3],[1,0],[6,1],[0,3],[5,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nG . . . . . .\n. # . . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . #\n. # . A . . .\n. . # . # . #\n. # . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left up up up up left left","env":"G . . . . . .\n. # . . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . #\n. # . A . . .\n. . # . # . #\n. # . . # . .\n","size":7,"actions":"left up up up up left left","numeric_actions":[3,0,0,0,0,3,3],"n_steps":7,"start_pos":[4,3],"goal_pos":[0,0],"obstacles":[[4,1],[5,4],[6,1],[6,4],[1,1],[3,6],[1,6],[5,6],[5,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . A\n. . . . .\n. G . . .\n# . . # .\n# . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down left down left left","env":"# . . . A\n. . . . .\n. G . . .\n# . . # .\n# . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"down left down left left","numeric_actions":[2,3,2,3,3],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[0,4],"goal_pos":[2,1],"obstacles":[[3,3],[0,0],[4,0],[3,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # # . . . . # . .\n. # . # . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . # .\n# . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . # # G\n# . . # . . # . . .\n. . . . # . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . # A . # . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up right up right up right up","env":". # # . . . . # . .\n. # . # . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . # .\n# . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . # # G\n# . . # . . # . . .\n. . . . # . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . # A . # . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"right up right up right up right up","numeric_actions":[1,0,1,0,1,0,1,0],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[8,5],"goal_pos":[4,9],"obstacles":[[7,8],[5,6],[4,7],[5,3],[3,0],[8,7],[2,8],[6,4],[7,0],[0,2],[1,3],[1,1],[0,7],[0,2],[0,1],[4,8],[2,3],[5,0],[7,8],[8,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . # . # . . .\n. . . . . G A . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n# . . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . . # . #\n. # . . # # . . # .\n# . . . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left","env":". # . . # . # . . .\n. . . . . G A . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n# . . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . . # . #\n. # . . # # . . # .\n# . . . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"left","numeric_actions":[3],"n_steps":1,"start_pos":[1,6],"goal_pos":[1,5],"obstacles":[[4,8],[4,3],[8,0],[6,2],[7,8],[7,1],[2,8],[0,6],[6,9],[0,1],[7,5],[0,4],[0,6],[3,0],[0,6],[6,2],[6,7],[8,6],[7,8],[7,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . . . . .\n. # . . # . . . . .\n. . . # . . # . # .\nA . . . . . . . . .\n# . # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. # # . . . # . . .\n# # . . . . . . # #\n. . . . . # . G # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right right down down down down right right right down","env":". . # . . . . . . .\n. # . . # . . . . .\n. . . # . . # . # .\nA . . . . . . . . .\n# . # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. # # . . . # . . .\n# # . . . . . . # #\n. . . . . # . G # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"right right right right down down down down right right right down","numeric_actions":[1,1,1,1,2,2,2,2,1,1,1,2],"n_steps":12,"start_pos":[3,0],"goal_pos":[8,7],"obstacles":[[6,6],[7,0],[6,6],[2,3],[7,0],[6,2],[7,9],[8,8],[4,2],[2,6],[7,8],[1,4],[8,5],[6,1],[4,0],[7,9],[1,1],[7,1],[0,2],[2,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . . . .\n. . . . # . #\n. # . . . . .\n. . . # . . #\n. . . # . . .\n. . . A . . .\n. G . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left down","env":". # . . . . .\n. . . . # . #\n. # . . . . .\n. . . # . . #\n. . . # . . .\n. . . A . . .\n. G . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"left left down","numeric_actions":[3,3,2],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[5,3],"goal_pos":[6,1],"obstacles":[[3,6],[4,3],[1,4],[1,6],[3,3],[0,1],[3,3],[2,1],[3,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # A .\n. . # . .\n. . . # G\n. . . . .\n. . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down down","env":". . # A .\n. . # . .\n. . . # G\n. . . . .\n. . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"right down down","numeric_actions":[1,2,2],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[0,3],"goal_pos":[2,4],"obstacles":[[0,2],[2,3],[1,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . .\n. # G . . .\n# . . . . .\n. . . . A .\n. . # . . #\n. . . . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"left up up left","env":"# . . . . .\n. # G . . .\n# . . . . .\n. . . . A .\n. . # . . #\n. . . . . #\n","size":6,"actions":"left up up left","numeric_actions":[3,0,0,3],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[3,4],"goal_pos":[1,2],"obstacles":[[4,5],[1,1],[4,2],[5,5],[2,0],[4,5],[0,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . # . . #\n. # . . # . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . # . . .\n# . . . # # . . . .\n. . . . # . . . . #\n. . . . # . . . . G\n. . # . . # . . . .\n. # . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . A .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up right up up","env":". . # . . . # . . #\n. # . . # . . . # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . # . . .\n# . . . # # . . . .\n. . . . # . . . . #\n. . . . # . . . . G\n. . # . . # . . . .\n. # . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . A .\n","size":10,"actions":"up right up up","numeric_actions":[0,1,0,0],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[9,8],"goal_pos":[6,9],"obstacles":[[0,2],[8,1],[7,2],[8,4],[3,2],[5,9],[5,4],[1,8],[4,0],[4,4],[1,1],[0,6],[4,4],[7,5],[6,4],[1,4],[4,5],[3,6],[0,9],[1,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . # . .\n# . . . . . .\n. . . # . . #\n. # . . # . .\n. . . A . # .\n. . # . . . .\n. G . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left down down","env":". . # . # . .\n# . . . . . .\n. . . # . . #\n. # . . # . .\n. . . A . # .\n. . # . . . .\n. G . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"left left down down","numeric_actions":[3,3,2,2],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[4,3],"goal_pos":[6,1],"obstacles":[[0,4],[3,1],[2,3],[1,0],[3,4],[4,5],[2,6],[0,2],[5,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . #\n. . . . G\n# . . # .\nA . . . .\n. . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right right up up","env":". . . . #\n. . . . G\n# . . # .\nA . . . .\n. . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"right right right right up up","numeric_actions":[1,1,1,1,0,0],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[3,0],"goal_pos":[1,4],"obstacles":[[2,0],[0,4],[2,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . # G # # .\n. . # . . . . . .\n# # . . . . . . .\n. # . # # # # . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . A . # .\n. . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up right up up up left left up up","env":". . . . # G # # .\n. . # . . . . . .\n# # . . . . . . .\n. # . # # # # . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . . . . A . # .\n. . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"right up right up up up left left up up","numeric_actions":[1,0,1,0,0,0,3,3,0,0],"n_steps":10,"start_pos":[6,5],"goal_pos":[0,5],"obstacles":[[3,6],[1,2],[5,1],[0,4],[7,3],[3,5],[2,0],[0,7],[3,1],[6,7],[3,3],[0,6],[0,6],[6,7],[3,4],[2,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . # . # . .\n. . . . . . . # .\n. # . # . # . # .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . G # .\n. # . # . . . . .\n. # . . . . A . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up up","env":". . . . # . # . .\n. . . . . . . # .\n. # . # . # . # .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . G # .\n. # . # . . . . .\n. # . . . . A . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"up up","numeric_actions":[0,0],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[7,6],"goal_pos":[5,6],"obstacles":[[1,7],[7,1],[2,5],[0,6],[8,4],[2,7],[6,1],[0,4],[2,1],[2,7],[5,7],[2,1],[6,3],[5,4],[2,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nG . . . #\n. # . . .\n. . . . .\n. . . . A\n. # . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left up up left left left","env":"G . . . #\n. # . . .\n. . . . .\n. . . . A\n. # . . #\n","size":5,"actions":"up left up up left left left","numeric_actions":[0,3,0,0,3,3,3],"n_steps":7,"start_pos":[3,4],"goal_pos":[0,0],"obstacles":[[4,1],[4,4],[0,4],[1,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . # .\n. . . . A . . . .\n# # . # . # . # .\n. G . . # . . . #\n. . . . . . . # #\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left down down left","env":". . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . # .\n. . . . A . . . .\n# # . # . # . # .\n. G . . # . . . #\n. . . . . . . # #\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . . . . .\n. . . . . # . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"left left down down left","numeric_actions":[3,3,2,2,3],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[2,4],"goal_pos":[4,1],"obstacles":[[1,7],[4,4],[3,0],[5,8],[4,8],[3,7],[2,4],[8,5],[7,3],[5,7],[8,5],[3,1],[7,3],[3,5],[3,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . G . . # # A .\n. . # . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. # # # . . . # .\n. # # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . . # . # . # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down left left up left left up left","env":"# . G . . # # A .\n. . # . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. # # # . . . # .\n. # # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n. # . . . . . . .\n. . . # . # . # .\n","size":9,"actions":"down down left left up left left up left","numeric_actions":[2,2,3,3,0,3,3,0,3],"n_steps":9,"start_pos":[0,7],"goal_pos":[0,2],"obstacles":[[3,1],[3,2],[8,5],[1,2],[3,3],[0,0],[4,1],[1,6],[6,4],[8,3],[7,1],[0,5],[3,7],[0,6],[8,7],[4,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # # # . . .\n. . . . . G . . .\n. A . # # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n# . . . . # # . #\n. . . . # . . # #\n# . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up right right right right","env":". . . # # # . . .\n. . . . . G . . .\n. A . # # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n# . . . . # # . #\n. . . . # . . # #\n# . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . . .\n","size":9,"actions":"up right right right right","numeric_actions":[0,1,1,1,1],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[2,1],"goal_pos":[1,5],"obstacles":[[0,5],[6,7],[4,4],[5,6],[5,8],[7,0],[0,3],[2,4],[8,0],[0,3],[2,3],[6,4],[5,5],[6,8],[0,4],[5,0]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . .\n# . . # .\nG . . . .\n. A . . #\n. . . # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left up","env":"# . . . .\n# . . # .\nG . . . .\n. A . . #\n. . . # .\n","size":5,"actions":"left up","numeric_actions":[3,0],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[3,1],"goal_pos":[2,0],"obstacles":[[1,0],[3,4],[1,3],[0,0],[4,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # # . . #\n. . . . . .\n. A # . . .\n. . . . . .\n. . G # # .\n. . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down right","env":". # # . . #\n. . . . . .\n. A # . . .\n. . . . . .\n. . G # # .\n. . . . . .\n","size":6,"actions":"down down right","numeric_actions":[2,2,1],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[2,1],"goal_pos":[4,2],"obstacles":[[2,2],[0,1],[4,3],[4,4],[0,5],[0,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nA . # # .\n. G # . .\n. . . . .\n. . . # .\n. # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right","env":"A . # # .\n. G # . .\n. . . . .\n. . . # .\n. # . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"down right","numeric_actions":[2,1],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[0,0],"goal_pos":[1,1],"obstacles":[[3,3],[1,2],[0,2],[0,3],[4,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # # . .\n. # # . # . .\n. . # . . . .\n. . G . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . A\n. . # # . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"up up left left left left","env":". . . # # . .\n. # # . # . .\n. . # . . . .\n. . G . . . .\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . . . A\n. . # # . . #\n","size":7,"actions":"up up left left left left","numeric_actions":[0,0,3,3,3,3],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[5,6],"goal_pos":[3,2],"obstacles":[[1,1],[2,2],[6,3],[0,3],[1,4],[0,4],[6,6],[1,2],[6,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . .\n. G . . . # #\n# . . . . . #\n. . . # # # .\n. . # . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . A . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left left left up up up up up","env":". . . . . . .\n. G . . . # #\n# . . . . . #\n. . . # # # .\n. . # . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . . . A . .\n","size":7,"actions":"left left left up up up up up","numeric_actions":[3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0],"n_steps":8,"start_pos":[6,4],"goal_pos":[1,1],"obstacles":[[3,3],[4,2],[1,5],[2,0],[3,4],[1,6],[2,6],[3,5],[4,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . A . # . . .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . # . # . # . .\n. # # . . . . . # .\n. . . . # . # . . .\n. # # . # . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . G .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down down down down right down down right right down right","env":". . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . A . # . . .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . # . # . # . .\n. # # . . . . . # .\n. . . . # . # . . .\n. # # . # . . . . #\n. . . # . . . . G .\n","size":10,"actions":"down down down down down right down down right right down right","numeric_actions":[2,2,2,2,2,1,2,2,1,1,2,1],"n_steps":12,"start_pos":[1,4],"goal_pos":[9,8],"obstacles":[[8,9],[7,4],[8,1],[5,5],[2,9],[3,3],[6,8],[1,4],[6,1],[5,0],[5,7],[8,4],[9,3],[7,6],[8,2],[5,3],[6,2],[1,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . . G . .\n. # # . . . . .\n. . # . . . # .\n. # . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . # . . # . .\n. . . . # . # .\n. A . . # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right up up up right right up up up up","env":". # . . . G . .\n. # # . . . . .\n. . # . . . # .\n. # . . # . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. . # . . # . .\n. . . . # . # .\n. A . . # . . .\n","size":8,"actions":"right right up up up right right up up up up","numeric_actions":[1,1,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,0,0],"n_steps":11,"start_pos":[7,1],"goal_pos":[0,5],"obstacles":[[3,4],[0,1],[6,6],[6,4],[1,2],[5,2],[1,1],[2,2],[2,6],[5,5],[3,1],[7,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . # .\n. . . G . # . . .\n. A . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n# . . . # . . . .\n# . . # # . . . .\n# . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . # . . #\n\nActions:\n","response":"up right right","env":". . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . # .\n. . . G . # . . .\n. A . . . # . . .\n. . . . . . # . .\n# . . . # . . . .\n# . . # # . . . .\n# . . . . . . . .\n. . . # . # . . #\n","size":9,"actions":"up right right","numeric_actions":[0,1,1],"n_steps":3,"start_pos":[3,1],"goal_pos":[2,3],"obstacles":[[2,5],[6,0],[5,4],[8,5],[6,4],[5,4],[6,3],[1,7],[6,3],[8,3],[7,0],[5,0],[8,8],[3,5],[4,6],[0,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . .\n. . . . G\n. # . . .\n. . . # A\n. . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up up","env":". . # . .\n. . . . G\n. # . . .\n. . . # A\n. . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"up up","numeric_actions":[0,0],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[3,4],"goal_pos":[1,4],"obstacles":[[2,1],[3,3],[0,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . # .\n. . . # . #\n. A # . . .\n. . # . . .\n. . . . . G\n. . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down right right right right","env":"# . . . # .\n. . . # . #\n. A # . . .\n. . # . . .\n. . . . . G\n. . . . . .\n","size":6,"actions":"down down right right right right","numeric_actions":[2,2,1,1,1,1],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[2,1],"goal_pos":[4,5],"obstacles":[[0,0],[1,3],[2,2],[1,5],[0,4],[0,4],[3,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . # . # #\n. . A . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. # . . . . # # # .\n. . . . . G . . . .\n. . # # # . . . # #\n. . # . . . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down right down down right right","env":". . . . . . . . . .\n# . . # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . # . # #\n. . A . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. # . . . . # # # .\n. . . . . G . . . .\n. . # # # . . . # #\n. . # . . . . # . .\n","size":10,"actions":"down right down down right right","numeric_actions":[2,1,2,2,1,1],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[4,2],"goal_pos":[7,5],"obstacles":[[3,9],[5,9],[8,9],[1,0],[2,8],[9,7],[6,7],[8,8],[3,8],[3,6],[8,3],[6,1],[8,2],[9,2],[4,5],[8,4],[6,8],[1,3],[6,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . .\n. . . # . .\nA . # . # .\n. G . . . #\n. # . . . .\n. . . . # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down","env":". . . . . .\n. . . # . .\nA . # . # .\n. G . . . #\n. # . . . .\n. . . . # .\n","size":6,"actions":"right down","numeric_actions":[1,2],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[2,0],"goal_pos":[3,1],"obstacles":[[2,2],[2,4],[4,1],[4,1],[3,5],[5,4],[1,3]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . # . .\n. . . . . .\n. G . . . #\n. . . # # .\n. . # . . .\nA . # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up up up","env":". . . # . .\n. . . . . .\n. G . . . #\n. . . # # .\n. . # . . .\nA . # . . .\n","size":6,"actions":"right up up up","numeric_actions":[1,0,0,0],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[5,0],"goal_pos":[2,1],"obstacles":[[3,3],[3,4],[5,2],[0,3],[4,2],[2,5]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# # # . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . # # # .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # . G . #\n. . . . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. # . . # . . . A #\n. . . . . . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left up up up","env":"# # # . # . . . . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . # . # # # .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # . G . #\n. . . . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . . . # .\n. # . . # . . . A #\n. . . . . . . # . .\n","size":10,"actions":"left up up up","numeric_actions":[3,0,0,0],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[8,8],"goal_pos":[5,7],"obstacles":[[5,9],[2,4],[0,0],[2,8],[8,1],[3,7],[7,8],[0,2],[0,4],[7,8],[8,4],[2,7],[8,9],[0,1],[5,5],[2,6],[6,5],[9,7],[8,8]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . . . . . .\n. . # # . # . . . .\n. . . G . . . . . .\n# . . # . . . # # .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . A . #\n. . . . . . . # # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up left up up left left left","env":". . # . . . . . . .\n. . # # . # . . . .\n. . . G . . . . . .\n# . . # . . . # # .\n. . . . . . . . . #\n. . . . . . . A . #\n. . . . . . . # # .\n. . . . . . . . . .\n. . # . . . . . # .\n. . . . . . . # . .\n","size":10,"actions":"up left up up left left left","numeric_actions":[0,3,0,0,3,3,3],"n_steps":7,"start_pos":[5,7],"goal_pos":[2,3],"obstacles":[[3,0],[0,2],[5,9],[3,7],[0,2],[3,3],[9,7],[3,0],[8,8],[1,2],[6,7],[1,5],[1,3],[3,8],[4,9],[6,8],[8,2],[1,5],[3,7]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . .\n. . . . #\n. . . A .\n. # # . G\n. . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down","env":". . . . .\n. . . . #\n. . . A .\n. # # . G\n. . . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"right down","numeric_actions":[1,2],"n_steps":2,"start_pos":[2,3],"goal_pos":[3,4],"obstacles":[[3,2],[3,1],[1,4],[1,4],[1,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . . . .\n. . # . . . .\n. . # . . A #\n# . . . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . # . . . G\n. . . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down right down","env":". # . . . . .\n. . # . . . .\n. . # . . A #\n# . . . . . #\n. . . . . . .\n. . # . . . G\n. . . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"down down right down","numeric_actions":[2,2,1,2],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[2,5],"goal_pos":[5,6],"obstacles":[[2,6],[2,6],[5,2],[3,0],[3,0],[2,2],[0,1],[1,2],[3,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\nA . . . #\n. . # . .\n. . G . .\n# . . # .\n. # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right down down right","env":"A . . . #\n. . # . .\n. . G . .\n# . . # .\n. # . . .\n","size":5,"actions":"right down down right","numeric_actions":[1,2,2,1],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[0,0],"goal_pos":[2,2],"obstacles":[[3,3],[0,4],[3,0],[4,1],[1,2]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # . . A\n# . . . . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . # . . . . . #\n. . . . . # # . .\n# . . # # # . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . G # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left down down down down down down left down","env":". . . . . . . . .\n. . . . . # . . A\n# . . . . # . . #\n. . . . . . . . #\n. . # . . . . . #\n. . . . . # # . .\n# . . # # # . . .\n. . . . # . . . .\n. . . . . . G # .\n","size":9,"actions":"left down down down down down down left down","numeric_actions":[3,2,2,2,2,2,2,3,2],"n_steps":9,"start_pos":[1,8],"goal_pos":[8,6],"obstacles":[[6,3],[2,0],[7,4],[1,5],[2,8],[8,7],[2,5],[3,8],[5,5],[4,8],[4,2],[6,0],[6,0],[5,6],[6,4],[6,5]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . G . #\n. . . . . . # . . .\n. # . # . # . . # .\n. . . . A . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . # . . .\n# # . . # . . . # .\n. . . . # # # . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"up up right up right right","env":". . . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . . # . .\n. . . . . . . G . #\n. . . . . . # . . .\n. # . # . # . . # .\n. . . . A . . . . .\n. # . . . . . . . .\n# . . . . . # . . .\n# # . . # . . . # .\n. . . . # # # . . .\n","size":10,"actions":"up up right up right right","numeric_actions":[0,0,1,0,1,1],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[5,4],"goal_pos":[2,7],"obstacles":[[1,0],[1,7],[8,8],[7,0],[9,4],[4,1],[9,5],[7,6],[9,4],[4,3],[8,0],[8,1],[2,9],[9,6],[8,4],[4,5],[6,1],[4,8],[3,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # G . . . # A\n. . . # . . # .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . # . . # . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. # . # . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"down down left left up left up left left","env":". # G . . . # A\n. . . # . . # .\n. . . # . . . .\n. . # . . # . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. # . . . . . .\n. . . . . . . .\n. # . # . . . .\n","size":8,"actions":"down down left left up left up left left","numeric_actions":[2,2,3,3,0,3,0,3,3],"n_steps":9,"start_pos":[0,7],"goal_pos":[0,2],"obstacles":[[2,3],[1,3],[7,3],[1,3],[5,1],[0,6],[7,1],[5,1],[3,2],[0,1],[3,5],[1,6]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . G . . .\n. . . . . #\n# . . . . .\n. . . . # .\n. . . . . .\nA . . . # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right up up up up up right","env":". . G . . .\n. . . . . #\n# . . . . .\n. . . . # .\n. . . . . .\nA . . . # .\n","size":6,"actions":"right up up up up up right","numeric_actions":[1,0,0,0,0,0,1],"n_steps":7,"start_pos":[5,0],"goal_pos":[0,2],"obstacles":[[3,4],[2,0],[1,5],[2,0],[5,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. # . . #\n. . . G .\n. . . . #\nA . . . .\n. . # # .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right up up","env":". # . . #\n. . . G .\n. . . . #\nA . . . .\n. . # # .\n","size":5,"actions":"right right right up up","numeric_actions":[1,1,1,0,0],"n_steps":5,"start_pos":[3,0],"goal_pos":[1,3],"obstacles":[[4,2],[0,1],[2,4],[4,3],[0,4]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n# . . . . . .\n# . # . . . .\n. # . . . . .\n. # . . . # .\n# . . # . . .\nA . . . G . .\n. # . . . . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"right right right right","env":"# . . . . . .\n# . # . . . .\n. # . . . . .\n. # . . . # .\n# . . # . . .\nA . . . G . .\n. # . . . . .\n","size":7,"actions":"right right right right","numeric_actions":[1,1,1,1],"n_steps":4,"start_pos":[5,0],"goal_pos":[5,4],"obstacles":[[3,1],[1,2],[0,0],[2,1],[4,0],[3,5],[1,0],[4,3],[6,1]]}
{"prompt":"Grid World:\n. . # . . A .\n. . . . . . .\n. . # . . . #\n. # . . . . .\n. . # # . . .\n. . . . G . .\n. # . # # . .\n\nActions:\n","response":"left down down down down down","env":". . # . . A .\n. . . . . . .\n. . # . . . #\n. # . . . . .\n. . # # . . .\n. . . . G . .\n. # . # # . .\n","size":7,"actions":"left down down down down down","numeric_actions":[3,2,2,2,2,2],"n_steps":6,"start_pos":[0,5],"goal_pos":[5,4],"obstacles":[[6,1],[4,3],[6,4],[6,3],[2,2],[3,1],[2,6],[4,2],[0,2]]}
